[Music]
D'Ise Laps stock was up 5% yesterday and
D region, by the way, the Q4 results which the company
declared on Saturday, so what was there
in the results or what did the
management say about them.  Due to which the
stock was up 5% yesterday. So
let's know in this video, first of all
we have to know how the company's AP
business, generic AP business has performed in
Q4. So basically, if I
explain to you in short, then the components of the company's
business in this are: Date is 1. This generic AP
business is the business of active pharmaceutical
ingredients. So the company does
not do any business in formulations.
It only supplies the APs which are required for formulations to its
clients
which are in countries like that and Europe.
Apart from this, the company has a custom synthesis business
where the company does drug development on a contract basis on
behalf of other companies.
So these are the business
components of the company. If you want to know in detail what are the
modes and risks of the company, then a
few days ago we did a video on this
where we observed the day from these two
lenses i.e. modes and
risks, the link of which I will give you
in the description box.  I will put it here, you
must check that video, so let's go to the Q4 results,
in this we see how the generic AP
business has performed, but the entire effort
23, so if we
look at the trade from Q4 in Q23, then here you will
see that the growth of the company was quite high in Q20 and Q21, in fact, a
little bit of growth was seen slowing down from Q19 to Q20 to Q21
and mainly here the
custom synthesis business of the company was doing well at
this time, but the
growth in effort 22 and 23 has been
seen in single digits, so generally the AP
business is going through a little bit of a slowing phase
in Q5 22 and 23,
but if we compare it with Q18, then the
company has achieved a growth of around 15% in its generic AP business, the
pricing pressure was very high in this business,
due to which the margins of the company have
also decreased a little here  The journey took place and
due to the Covid related AP business, very good revenues were generated in Effort 21 and F22
and currently whatever revenue has come in Effort 23 has
come from other therapies. Good volume group has been seen in the drugs of other therapies. So,
after this one code, a structural change
is visible here that the company will now
go into other therapies where the sustainable level of
volume will be quite strong. Now let's
talk about the other segment of the company,
this custom synthesis business. The
cyclicality of revenue here is
very high. If you look at the 22nd and
brilliant year, the company in the custom
synthesis business, where they earned a
revenue of about Rs 4.5 thousand crore in this one
financial year, from there, in
Effort 23 which has just ended, there was a
growth of almost 32% in their numbers
and in the region wise co-award
related to D, there was a custom synthesis drug whose
name was  Molno Pyramid: Its revenue
decreased significantly in Effort 23.
This was one reason why the company was
doing very well in the custom synthesis business and
obviously due to this the revenue
decreased. The company faced a lot of problems in the custom synthesis business.
In Effort 23,
you try and make a difference. The number of margins
and revenue decreased. So this was one reason why custom
synthesis had come a long way. But
if we look at the historical scenario, the custom synthesis
business is always long in nature, that is,
sometimes a lot of business comes to the company at the same time
and during this period,
we see a little slowing business because
basically this
business is dependent on the demand from the customer. Due to this, the cyclical
element
of the company in the custom synthesis business is quite high.
Now let's talk about margins.
We have talked about it so far. It is
also important for us to know what is the condition of the revenue margins
if we look at Q4.  If you look at the margins of F523, the debt
margin is around 25% and the
paste margin is around 16%. You
will have a graph on your screen right now where you will see
how good the margins were for the company last year, i.e. FY22. There were some
quarters where the company made half the
margin of almost 44%. Obviously, cost
pressures started coming and revenue
pressures also started coming. Due to both, the current
company seems to be forming a bottom.
In terms of margins,
after many quarters, the
company's margins have been seen at such low levels. On
evidence, both levels are at such low levels. So why are the margins decreasing? Is that the reason why
its
margins are falling so
much? First of all, revenue is
decreasing a lot because obviously all
margins are related to revenue.
When revenue decreases, obviously
operating leverage works on the down side as well. So
there  Obviously, the company's costs
appear to be higher as a percentage of revenue,
but the cost of materials has
also increased. So, since the last Air Effort 23
started, the company's raw
material costs also started increasing
and due to the decrease in debt, at a time when revenue was
already decreasing, so obviously the cost as a
percentage of sales increased and automatically the
margins also started decreasing a lot.
But what has the company
said about Q4, so basically a little trend is
visible here in terms of margins that
perhaps the worst phase in terms of low
margins may have ended here. It seems that the
company had
a unit three in Kakinada. The company
currently has two units and the third unit is
under construction. So, this
facility of Kakinada was
also in legal trouble from a long time, so the company got
clearance from there and the company got clearance from K4.  It is
said that they are going to invest
around 1200 to 1500 crores for this plant,
where the
manufacturing and supply of the company will
start, but the starting
materials are intermediate AP, all these three
things which are required for EPF, so
their manufacturing will start here, the
company has said this, by the end of the
current year of FI 24, after about two and a half years,
this complete commercialization of this facility will start, the
company has said this in its statement,
obviously this will increase the capacity of the company,
so that is some good
sentiment from the investors' point of view,
and in the rest of the custom synthesis business of the company,
some new products have
come there, where commercial production will
start soon, the company has said this,
and the raw material prices also
seem to be softening a bit, that is, they are seen to be decreasing, the
management has also said this for the EPFO ​​business, so all these
things happened in the Q4 results.  Is it a good time to
invest in this company
or not? If the price of this company has
fallen so much, then is this a good
time to invest in this company?
For this also, we made a video a few days ago
where Parimal Sir has done
a scenario
analysis of DBZ Lab in great detail. So I will paste the link of that too
in the description box here.
So do check out this video
further. Well, I hope you must have understood from this video
how the Q4 results were for DBZ and why the stock was down by 5% yesterday. Do
like this video, comment
and share it with maximum people and do
not forget to check out yesinvesting.in
where there are many financial
products like our model
portfolio where you can get 30%
discount if you use it. Do remember the coupon code.
We do not have any partnership with anyone. What
we do is on the model portfolio
and this is the benefit of our customer. So
I hope you will visit jarur.in. Will meet
in the next video. Thank you. So match
[music]